what's your favorite childhood memory
and why anything you took part in a swim
team
what do you think my favorite childhood
memory is what about visiting China
like just playing outside I'm not good
at remembering my childhood I learned to
ride a bicycle yeah that was good I
remember how you took my training wheels
off right well the first thing to teach
you is that you know I can still ride a
bike what's the most fun you've had with
me and why okay I think I should need to
think about watching jeopardy or try to
prove that we are the smartest import in
the world let's share I look for it
actually yes it's more corrector than
I've learned from the best
what's the most ridiculous thing I have
done what did it teach you about me I
don't think I've ever done anything
ridiculous okay sure I think tricky
waters I think right now something
ridiculous you're doing is digging our
basement another person told you I need
to take out the trash to avoid
tell me what you remember from the first
time we met and how it felt horrible so
who do you were born to this world yeah
how did that work it was one of the most
proudest moments I would probably look
at disgusting and covered in crab right
as I remember your first smart then you
start to cry before you cry you first
why that's an emotional rollercoaster
birth is exciting and then right now I
think what are you hesitant to tell me
something wrong I think maybe talking
about my emotions but I'm pretty
hesitant to talk about my emotions with
anybody you tried to conceal something
right no not really
what are the three funniest but that's
crossed out now it says best memories
that we shared when we went to China
together twice yeah the second time so
that counting is two of the three I
introduced many Chinese attractions to
you yeah including that wax museum that
you hated okay Dee Sangha you only had
to do we need to say sorry
they're filming us we have to you have
to get all three of us good thing to do
Oh again this time we do it toward
France for the first time it's true it
was very good
it seems like many of them are together
now if you would wish one thing for me
what would it to be one thing for me to
do going back to me emotions question
clearly when was the time you're proud
of me and why and obviously I know when
you work in the White House that made me
so happy at the top of this world
yeah and for that we were even able to
visit the Oval Office
everybody will have this chance
what's that my time yeah okay
what do you think my best qualities is a
father there's enough digital tape to
roll this could go for hours you're
extremely integral and intelligent and
have such a strong work ethic that I
think is really inspirational yeah
there's like a million things you're
funny you pursue things that you believe
in you're honest what have I done or
what happened to me that scared you the
most and why
remember I told you not to walk late
night
if there's no more bus city bus you can
call me I just told you yeah you could
not just walk and that scares you yeah
sorting but I'm super tough yeah call me
I'll keep on my phone I'll come to you
for myself just for safety yeah safely
surprise always priority I grab a tissue
actually Thanks sorry that's okay I
think it'll be something more than this
actually Thanks no it's my turn
yeah I have industrial-grade it's not so
this is perfect what do you think is
special about already I think you're
right yeah right so what do you think is
special about our relationship I don't
know I think we have a lot of common
interests which sometimes is unusual
between parent and child so that's
special what do you think is special
mm-hmm no animosity true and also pipe
something as you understand even every
day night we cook Mew together we
cooperate so we're cooking dream team
everyone is invited to partake if you
could go back in time what would you
change
I don't know if this question means like
everything like you could kill Hitler or
that pertains to our life that's certain
you would have regret all the time
something would think if I do it again I
would do different yeah yeah is there
like a specific thing specific progress
or not sometimes should not push people
so hard a little bit patient just a
little bit when I try occasion road-rage
less what's the greatest lesson I taught
you
I think being an integral person who
works really hard for not really for
other people but for yourself and for
other people obviously you do it for us
putting yeah I don't know a lot of
things and be persistent yeah no Brooke
what's the word Prague Prague now what's
always daily always progressive
progressive which is of course how do
you feel about my procrastination
progress dick right procrastination
procrastination okay what's one lesson
or idea you want me to never forget said
again what one lesson our idea you you
want me to never forget I would say just
try to pursue your own dream or go
processing today never be afraid of any
difficulties even if my dream is to be a
waitress
okay so there's an asterisk what's a
question you always wanted to ask me I
think I always want to ask you about
your like your childhood in your history
like always curious to know more
especially cultural revolution like
where things happen during your time
even to today I could not believe that
happened to me
yeah I want to hear I feel like me and
how en don't know like even close to
some of this stuff the schools were
closed that's just unbelievable
yeah who's ever happened to a whole
country totally crazy well we don't
really like to know anything about it
like your personal experience I think
it'd be really interesting because no
score was sent to effect you to work as
a laborer yeah ten years hard time
that's it but I feel like there's more
than just like we know that what we do
you know that's on the other side it
made me even stronger I guess how time
made me stronger
all right no it's my tone your tongue
how am I most like you and how does that
scare you oh oh how am I most like you
and how does that scare you seems to be
a loaded question you like me yeah and
like how does it scare you or like to
read write or like watch trivial
question programs like yeah I think but
there's no skill me I feel good we have
comedy yeah I guess maybe this question
is trying to ask are there any sort of
traits that you don't have that you to
possess yeah that you also have accepted
for I mentioned procrastination that's
something you don't have that you're not
a procrastinator so it's like what are
traits that you see in me that you also
have that you wish weren't there I guess
do we spend enough time together
obviously not yeah when you were at the
school together only do something
innovative together
what's your fondest memory from your
childhood and why actually I think I'm
on my childhood memory obviously no as I
said life that time was very tough for
me only some time we could not or even
watch movie there's any glimmer my
family was kind of poor so is there any
anything you couldn't pull out the only
thing I feel proud of myself so I took
an interest examination got into the
best Middle School in Shanghai yeah
that's my proudest time yeah no it's not
how can I be a bad parent means I'm not
better enough yeah like how can I
improve upon already being the best
parent is what it should say I think
just why is it early I think if you I
want you to take care of yourself better
it's like being a pig it's not about
parenting no but that is because of that
I mean you can't be a parent if you're
not there and in good health and
condition so I would say that's a
prerequisite think about Karen being a
human I'll maybe try to earn more money
enough to bring back all your bread
bread butter and bread yeah we eat
really well we talked about that it's
not about that okay sorry
flip that'd be great
I'm kind of a phlegm factory thank you
do you mean of question I can't think
about head start okay tell me about a
moment that changed you in life then I
would say when I got accepted by Chinese
government as a student to study in a
mark
certainly totally changed my life
otherwise you will not be born in this
country and I would not be able to come
out to the outside world to see what
really is like in the United States
because in past you know China always
portrayed America as the bet the worst
enemy of China
q us a chance
how did it having me as a father shaped
shape you not shape you having me every
shape well you taught me impeccable
grammar corrected this card I think that
it's really like I mentioned earlier a
lot of it's instilled in me like a good
work ethic and caring about other people
that's sheep all right integrity totally
rock-solid integrity how do you think I
would be different if you stayed in
China if I stay don't you stay if you
stay there how would I be different you
will not be coming to this world I mean
China's only sign already your president
this interview would look like this yes
second chapter you will be talking tears
I hope you know you look crazy okay
that's cool okay what's the one quality
you have you you never want me to change
and why one quality you never want me to
change my humor even if you wanted to
change no okay I can tell one more thing
yeah oh this after I went to swim in a
pool the first time I went to the
Metropolitan Avenue swim before and I
asked her later inside the water is
there
fast and slow land difference she said
why this is this Medianet I like this
for mediocre people she said no no no no
humor goes over people's head but not my
head because I think it's the best
what's the hardest thing about being a
father thing I guess just tried to be
honest so sometimes it's a necessary not
to tell the truth at work yesterday this
woman came in with her daughter and we
have a roof with a pool at the
restaurant and she told me to tell her
daughter she told me she was like can I
ask you a question like can you do a
favor for me and I was like what's going
on this is weird and she's like can you
tell my daughter that the pool is closed
even though I was open so that I like
wintered the daughter and told her at
the pool was closed and she was crying
it seemed like a pretty crazy thing to
ask a waitress actually this mother
should be sued no I was like more of my
moral compass that's a little bit off
but then she told me if they're under
five it's okay to lie to them okay now
it's your toes turn let's see
thank you once okay so I think it's my
turn what do you think I forget or fail
to notice about myself and you we talked
about taking care of myself again I
forget or fail to notice about myself
yeah I think that I think
not to eat any crap food yeah except now
I think you're aware of that as you just
said that makes me think like you're
aware but you still do it I think you
forget if you could change one thing
about me aside for me waitressing right
now what would it be and why maybe also
just you need to take care yourself you
always urge you to put on enough closes
if the temperature gets cold right you
need to pay a tax right yeah that's a
pretty easy change I'll just wear socks
worth when what was the toughest
toughest toughest moment in our
relationship and how do you feel about
it now what was the toughest moment in
our relationship any like a special
milestone of toughness this day maybe
just the fact that you were in New York
and we were in Alabama that's tough when
you were young right yeah that's because
I had to find a job on Obama that's why
I don't okay what are you worried about
for me and my future aside from being
waitressing forever
you need to be decisive right sometimes
you to be too hesitant to do yeah you'll
always feel difficult making choice
making right decisions have this quality
the decisiveness
what's a pain in me you would like to
hear is this kind of a metaphor looking
is a real thing or metaphor I feel like
it probably comes encompasses emotional
pain whatsapp if I could erase your bad
childhood I would do that do you think
I'll be a good mother and wife I will
rather hold on to the judgment for them
which as the blood you did to Hillary
Clinton hold on his endorsement so you
have to prove yourself to be I cannot
endorse you for the moment why do you
love me what's your absolute favorite
thing about me I'll see you understand
all my jokes next thing I like right as
you say sometimes I went to a place
taking it 20 and joke people will just
look and have kids to have an audience
y'all know the same jokes yeah that's
kind of understanding okay so there
shall be no more question yes there
should be a waiter standing here you
mean you producer person right on the
spot what do you most admire about me I
feel like we had a variation on this
question buddy and I would say still
here your work ethic and integrity is
very admirable and inspiration what
experience did you miss out on by being
a father I guess I would miss if there
could never be a millionaire like Donald
Trump to have a private jet I think
you're missing out on that just because
of us and not can never provide that
kind of luxury
yeah oh but no it says what experience
did you miss out on by being a father
like because you've had us like what
were you not able to do because you had
to really hear about us yeah I think
that's what it's trying to say that's
how it's like you know maybe why should
I miss out anything if I'm a father
right I'm a happy to have one son one
daughter
that's perfect combination you cannot
ask for more even the prince and
princesses only gather just son or
daughter just recently we have earlier
totally one-up that British royalty all
right that's the end of discussion
you have any question how you got into
this idea for me I feel obliged to to
obey to follow this is yeah this whole
experiment is just about following rules
but looks at it's it's a good thing
right
we never take the same chance at home to
talk to each other seriously so it gives
us a good opportunity to face each other
now face a nation face each other